<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elisabeth Graf</title>
    <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Elisabeth Graf</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://graf-lil.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Working Papers Graf, E., Kuhn, J. T., &amp;amp; McElvany, N. (2024). Domain-specific career aspirations, motivation, and achievement in math and reading across adolescence [manuscript in preparation]. TU Dortmund University.
Journal Articles Graf, E., Partheymüller, J., Bronner, L., &amp;amp; Kritzinger, S. (2024). Revisiting eligibility effects of voting at 16: Insights from Austria based on regression discontinuity analyses. Electoral Studies 92, Article 102870. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.electstud.2024.102870 OSF
Graf, E., Donath, J. L., Botes, E., Voracek, M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>About me I am &amp;hellip;.
Publications Here you can find a list of my publication, conference presentations, and talks.
Contact </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clean White Theme for Hugo</title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/post/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/post/readme/</guid>
      <description>Clean White Theme for Hugo CleanWhite is a clean, elegant, but fully functional blog theme for Hugo. Here is a live demo site using this theme.
It is based on huxblog Jekyll Theme and Clean Blog Jekyll Theme.
These two upstream projects have done awesome jobs to create a blog theme, what I&amp;rsquo;m doing here is porting it to Hugo, of which I like the simplicity and the much faster compiling speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Zhaohuabing Blog</title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/2017/11/03/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/2017/11/03/hello-world/</guid>
      <description> “Yeah It&amp;rsquo;s on. ”
Hello World! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Welcome to my personal website! I am a post-doctoral researcher at the TU Dortmund University, Center for Research on Education and School Development (IFS). I obtained my PhD in psychology at the VDS CoBeNe and was working as university assistant at the Department of Developmental and Educational Psychology at the University of Vienna. I am conducting empirical research in the field of education, mainly using quantitative methods. My main research interests are academic emotions, motivation, civic education, and political socialization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>About Me I am currently working as a PostDoc at the TU Dortmund, Center for Research on Education and School Development (IFS). I am conducting empirical research in the field of education, mainly using quantitative methods. My main research interests are academic emotions, motivation, civic education, and political socialization.
Work Experience PostDoc at the Center for Research on Education and School Development (IFS), TU Dortmund University, Dortmund, Germany; 1.11.2024 - now PostDoc at FAIR, Center for Research on Education and School Development (IFS), TU Dortmund University, Dortmund, Germany; 01.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/impressum/</guid>
      <description>Elisabeth Graf
Center for Research on Education and School Development (IFS) Martin-Schmeißer-Weg 13 44227 Dortmund
Kontakt
Telefon: +49 231 755 4994 E-Mail: elisabeth2.graf@tu-dortmund.de</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/search/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/search/placeholder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>University Courses University of Vienna As a University assistant, I have taught a seminar about &amp;ldquo;Political Identity Development and Civic Education&amp;rdquo; (MA Psychology, specialization in developmental and educational psychology) and a course about Science communication (BA Psychology). You can find an overview of my courses at the University of Vienna via ufind</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts Archive</title>
      <link>https://graf-lil.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graf-lil.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
